startech.com 2013-11-25

# Privacy Statement | StarTech.com

Effective: 01/04/2011

StarTech.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our web sites and promotions. You can help us to ensure your privacy, by not sharing your account user name or password with anyone. StarTech.com has established this privacy policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information.

StarTech.com is a licensee of the Trust-Guard Privacy Policy Verification Service. Trust-Guard is an independent organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet, by promoting the use of fair information practices. We want to demonstrate our commitment to maintaining your privacy, by agreeing to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by Trust-Guard.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first visit [Tech Support](https://www.startech.com/TechSupport). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact Trust-Guard. Trust-Guard will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

### Registration

In order to make a purchase from our website or register an account with us, you must submit personal information to the site in order for us to fulfill your requests for products and services. This information will include your name, email address, phone number, credit card information and address. Your contact information will also be collected by us, in the event that you contact us for sales or support help. You may access this information in order to update or change it at any time, by logging into the web site and going to your “My Account” page when logged in.

Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

### Security

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, Cybersource®, keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

We take every precaution to protect our users' personal information and to store it securely. We protect your credit card information and other sensitive personal information by using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology (the industry standard security protocol), hosting our site on secure servers, and maintaining Secure Site status from Geotrust owned by VeriSign, the security industry leader. We also have our web site tested daily by McAfee Secure™, a security scanning and reporting service, to ensure our site is safe from hacking. In addition, access to all of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Your information is safely stored behind a firewall that protects it from users from other networks. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.  

### Catalogs and Flyers

We require only the personal information that is needed for safely processing your online order and for contacting you about your transactions. It is used exclusively for that purpose. If you become a StarTech.com customer, you may receive mailings from your account information and your account information may be analyzed as part of our standard business practices. 

### Surveys and Contests

Periodically, we invite users to provide information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice as to whether or not to disclose requested contact information (such as name and mailing address) and demographic information (such as zip code/postal code or job title). In addition to other uses set forth in this policy, contact information collected in connection with surveys and contests is used to notify the winners and award prizes, to monitor or improve the use and satisfaction of the site. 

### Service Providers

We will share your information with companies who provide specific services to us such as shipping and the processing of your credit card information. We have contracts written with these companies and we review their privacy and security practices thoroughly before selecting them to provide our services. These companies are not allowed to use the information we provide to them for any reason, other than what it is they are contracted to do. The Live Chat function on our web site is also considered a service provider; your name will be collected for the sole purpose of providing you with a more personalized experience on their hosted site. 

### E-mail Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information such as name, e-mail address and, occasionally, demographic information. We use this information in the same manner as we use contact information in the registration and ordering process described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of all e-mail newsletters, at any time. 

### Cookies and Web Tracking

Some parts of StarTech.com's website use cookies to track user traffic patterns and to remember which country you have set. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information and to give the user the best possible web experience. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The web tracking cookies only track usage and general page visitation and trends and do not record personal information. 

### Correct inaccurate Information

You can update your basic account information at any time. To correct any other account information, please contact your account manager. We will attempt to keep customer information complete, up to date, and accurate. 

### Removal From StarTech.com Lists

You may receive periodic emails or postal mailings from us with information on new products and services, or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive e-mail and/or postal mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email at [support@startech.com](mailto:support@startech.com). StarTech.com does not currently rent, sell or otherwise forward your name or other personal information to other companies. 

### Links To Other Sites

It is important for StarTech.com users to realize that StarTech.com's privacy policy applies solely to information collected on this Site. Although the Site contains links to other sites, StarTech.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. For privacy information regarding other sites, please refer to their individual privacy policies. 

### Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information, as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

### Testimonials

We have posted testimonials on our web site that include the display of personal information. These testimonials were collected offline and the individuals who provide them also give StarTech.com expressed consent to place their personal information in a public area. 

### Business Transitions

In the event StarTech.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or a prominent notice on our website 30 days prior to any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**StarTech.com USA LLP**  
6300 Commerce Center Drive, Suite E  
Groveport OH  
43125
